a nail into the coffin of this whole aero solar fiasco because it's just so easy to do based off
of what she swore under penalty of perjury right like repeatedly what uh maybe three times here
and this uh eight page statement alone so here's number count number one right i mean
let's see we can use like uh preview to markup okay then uh here's count number one okay oops
so one okay
here's two
there's three okay so that's that's three uh sworn statements that were false materially false
because uh whether there were actually any threats plays a vital role in meeting the uh legal criteria
required by californian civil and uh civil stalking and harassment statutes the actual statutes right
uh i mean criminal uh stalking and harassment statutes are more severe so we'll just go with
civil for now and um i can show you that i don't meet civil criteria for either of these so i mean
you can look at the criminal yourself later if you want but um so civil this is penal code criminal
stocking civil code uh establishes the tort of stocking laws and distribution versus civil remedies
against oh okay so this is uh torts law this isn't um so there's only criminal stocking it's defined as
willfully maliciously i mean i can go with civil stocking for sure this is tort law this isn't
enforceable unless she sues but uh it has to meet all three elements right and one of them is a credible
threat there were no threats uh we'll soon go over that point like a billion times because there's only
eight pages of this and it's so easy to do anyway so uh i don't need the credible threat requirement for
civil stocking under california law under california penal code stalking i don't meet the credible threat
uh requirements because it has to
defined as willful maliciously repeatedly following or harassing another person combined
with making a credible threat to intended to place that person in reasonable fear
their safety or the safety of me so like it seems like i didn't do any of this but they read the
statute and then they just started lying um under oath and that had obviously material impact if
that was considered by the judge uh which it should have been because it's a requirement to meet these
statutory requirements right uh so there's no threats and then
the harassment wasn't even like well knowing and willful uh because um it's hard to explain amphetamine
poisoning but a person really unable to make rational thought and i never actually thought uh
hey i'm going to intentionally cause
officially torment terrorize or
even seriously alarm i may have subconsciously tried to annoy her a little
uh i mean that was truthfully what was going through my mind but it's not important because i i
failed the threat criteria here right oops so
let's uh go with california criminal harassment requires a credible threat again oh look that word
keeps popping up right
these people are like disgusting but uh so
uh and then it has to be willful malicious and repeated okay so willful again is it's hard to
establish i think for them uh i'd be happy to upload all of the i message exports publicly and
then you can decide for yourself whether any of it was willful or displayed a pattern of
willful behavior beyond a reasonable doubt but again you know it's just the threat criteria that's the only
one that they rely on and then they lie about and then they like it touches it really whatever
so it also requires intent which again uh i'm arguing that i had none and i'd be happy to upload
all of it and then people can decide for themselves whether a uh displayed intent beyond reasonable
debt or not so civil harassment under california is defined as unlawful violence a credible threat of
violence again the threat just keep coming up here right or a willful conduct directed at another
person that seriously annoys alarms or harasses them with analogous purposes causing substantial emotional
distress so let's see what are all of the requirements so which so one five two seven point six yeah uh
okay so
of course of conduct okay so person is severed
harassment okay okay okay okay okay of course conduct
people threat of violence harassment is unlawful
violence so they define harassment as unlawful violence a credible threat of violence or no
knowing and willful of course gone directed at a specific person that seriously annoys
harasses persons there's no legitimate purpose right so of course conduct must uh
uh uh be that which causes a reasonable person to suffer substantial emotional distress
and actually causes specialness and actually causes potentially emotional distress
to the petitioner so that that part i like the challenge as well
so uh so she filed her she signed her ch 110
on july 25th
july 25th
july 25th right
uh
i swear i'm done with this after i drafted this file that because it's
idiotic i don't want to take my time doing this so uh
so um all of the stuff that she alleges uh occurred before july 25th
um
where is um
oh here
uh okay let's jump to that part later but here's another con here's a contradiction and
uh uh an actor perjury she's claiming that there should be no filing fee because
uh she's alleging threats to use violence uh meet the legal definition of stocking which we just
went over
were acted in a way that somehow makes her reasonably fear violence right
so she's claiming that but earlier in the same petition she also claimed
did this person use or threatened to use a gun or any other weapon
she claimed no so what like okay let's review the civil
stalking statute like what is she talking about here if she claims that i never
threatened to use a weapon is she claiming that i threatened to like
like like like what i don't understand what she's talking about when she's uh alleging threats um
like is she alleging that i threatened to like go to like twitch's office and beat her up or something
like like what what logical possibilities remain i don't know but um
so
again again the the stalking statute requires a credible threat so um
um uh that fails right so the only uh
legal statute that she she could be relying on here
is the existence of threats which there weren't i mean okay anyways
so i i discovered all these like uh medium articles from members of the twitch community
who claimed to be her defenders right um in july and i believe i texted them to her uh
probably it or definitely tweeted about them and uh who knows how she uh i mean i think touch trust
and safety got involved it was a little obvious but i have no idea she uh how she didn't doesn't
disclose how much information she obtained from uh my public tweets right or from the articles from
her church community or from conversations that she had with trust and safety um an organization
uh but you know that doesn't matter the truth of what happened and i believe i can prove it too with
a guy message uh since before uh july 23rd was that i discovered like all this garbage
sometime in july and then i like texted her about it and then um
like these morons caused so much anxiety for me that um i felt like i needed to abuse more
amphetamine to be able to defend myself and respond so i sort of just uh wrote whatever the
hell i wanted to write under like those conditions of mental awareness and sent them
so that explains everything here right um okay so let's see
uh so i mean their community
accuses me of
i believe harassing pokemon or something when i called out her
fraudulent contract the claiming that i took her contract too literally because
well was it disclosed anyways uh i mean here's twitch's terms of sale
honestly english is my second language but so i'm not sure if my like comprehension abilities is
sufficient enough to understand the legal criteria of using twitch but um let's see
i promise to disclose it's all your benefits right uh
some services touch me offer certain ancillary products and services in connection with it
twitch services on a subscription basis right uh this is subscription products yeah it was right okay
all right as disclosed to you when you subscribe to any subscription service so is this disclosed to
you when you subscribe okay so that's that's the legal documents that twitch wrote okay then uh what
they forced users to agree to when users uh use their service right uh and then they also say that
broadcaster offered benefits may elect to offer whatever as ancillary products or services including
uh subscription services uh broadcast offer benefit is solely the obligation of the broadcaster offering
them and twitch bears no responsibility for it so i mean so under twitch's terms of sale they
they claim that uh ancillary benefits are clearly disclosed uh and that um you know that they claim that
twitch bears no responsibility for uh fraud committed by their broadcasters um i'm actually arguing that uh
they provided material support to their broadcasters uh because pokemon is a partner uh to twitch and i
believe she signed additional uh contracts beyond the uh traditional um you know the basic uh partnership or
whatever agreement or whatever agreement right anyways whatever so i just read some english and you know
put this uh on here and then uh complained about uh this fraud right because it's right here in english right
so
okay
so i like to create a little bit of a backstory that made sense and these people just keep running with it but um
um
okay so i offered a uh encouraging comments when why am i wasn't even talking about her publicly
uh i told twitter that she would do great in life um and then uh er defenders claimed that um
uh i shouldn't be saying anything because
uh people don't like
no not people just women they only claim that women don't like stalkers drug addicts and people who abuse
women interesting
this is gonna get very interesting uh in the future
but
okay so this there's not much here so one thing i like to point out is that um
there's a great creator on youtube uh called named john hammond
he uh does a lot of uh
lightning like introductory cyber security cyber threat uh videos
um so i don't know why i was arguing with these morons on twitter but
i believe i claimed that his
oh what does this guy claim
oh so i claimed that his content was not scripted which means uh it wasn't following
a screenplay right what's a screenplay like stupid like people are so fucking retarded like
uh does john hammond follow scripted like screenplays and youtube videos
while he may prepare outlines or notes to ensure clarity of thoroughness his delivery appears to be
natural and conversational suggests that he does not strictly adhere to a scripted screenplay this approach
allows him to effectively share his experience and insight with his audience right so
i mean like i'll just like briefly look at it
okay uh okay so let's see it's an interesting one
i mean okay oh okay uh whatever i just this is the last one i watched so is this scripted like no
yes plural code give me that but now let's build out another asynchronous function so he's obviously not
um he doesn't have a screenplay of what he's gonna write line by line so it's not scripted right but this
moron has to claim that i made myself look stupid to not be able to tell the difference between
scripted and non-scripted content like is he a fucking twitch fan or something what what problem
does he have with like content creation jokes um
he contradicts himself yes he might get the odd things i mean it's not like getting it wrong it's called
being human not being able to type everything perfectly all the time right like uh
anyway just another personal insult based off of a false premise and twitch likes to make a lot of
those uh in order to establish their you know grounds for personal insults and i believe um they deserve
to be exposed uh so i think i was going to touch on one other medium article um pull it up real quick
all right all right i mean so we're dealing with large amounts of like criminal assholes who are
obviously immoral um that the entire world could see i believe there are very easy solutions to these
problems and uh i don't know when i'm going to get to it but uh i mean whatever so
okay so uh see again this person who is named justice for samantha referring to aerosolar
claims that i've been criminally stalking her or at least civilly stalking her
because i did watch
saved all her images and videos to my computer and synced it oh no so like
all right so i believe he was referring to this script right uh which calls the touch api
um it gets all the streams of a particular streamer and then it downloads them 10 threads at a time
uh i think there's like 10 or so aerosolar streams that i saved so this must have finished
like 20 minutes or something and then i um synced into my cloud storage oh no so he's accusing me
of violating either criminal or civil stalking statutes because i'll use this script like
probably 20 lines if you just write the part for this and he's claiming that i need legal intervention
and the police needs to be made aware of the amount of evidence of stalking and abuse so what evidence
did he refer to post a library image which showed that he has stopped a poor woman and saved a lot of
social media and video so i ran this script i saved it on cloud storage and the police needs to be made
aware of this evidence interesting uh they're saying that i live in burlington massachusetts and that if you
know who to contact to help him please reference these medium articles and his twitter as he needs help
so what do they mean by help i believe that's a threat uh is this a threat that sounds like a threat
uh let's compare this to oh did we go through all of the eight pages yet okay so uh sorry uh
it's very easy right so is there a threat here no no no no no no no nope nope nope nope nope
nope nope nope what else is there nope nope nope nope nope nope and that's it but uh her community is
claiming that if you know who to contact to get him help please reference these medium articles
and his twitter as he needs help so what do they mean by that can they at least be honest in uh
about anything because that is so sad if they lack the basic integrity to tell the truth
about what they're doing anyways uh so her lawyers i think uh put the nail in her coffin
their lawyers claim that uh in support of her petition aerosol produced evidence of sexually
implicit threatening and uh blah blah blah okay so aerosol only produced one piece of evidence
exhibit b declaration of samantha briasko stewart this is the only piece of evidence right and okay
we can go through these eight pages again no threats no threats no threats no threats no threats
no threats no threats no threats no threats no threats no threats no threats i mean like i need like
a bot to like say this on youtube over and over again but i mean i'll upload this um
on the on the youtube link so people could look at the eight pages themselves so there were never any
threats despite uh three instances of perjury here and uh one here um that's contradicted by here so
there's four on her statements uh there are two separate statements uh both um governed by california's
perjury law uh ch120 form and then her uh exhibit b a page statement plus exhibits right uh so there's
you know three in their statements and then three counts of uh uh perjury for the threats part alone
and then uh one count in her ch120 right i'm also accusing her of another account of like provable
perjury and in uh her false assert uh her false accusations that she uh blocked my i message when
she actually didn't um and uh as a result she like lied to the courts about whether uh it was consensual or
not and whether i actually made new accounts to text her when she blocked me so it's you know raises
questions of whether she was uh consistently receiving this stuff then lying about it and then
using it against me in court right so i'm almost finished with the draft for the motion to appeal
and um that will be uh filed tomorrow and after that i think i'm done with this garbage because
this is a waste of time um i really wish that things played out differently and uh none of this
happened i mean i believe that it is important for people to at least attempt to make a positive
change in society for twitch overall but there's no reason to drag this particular individual uh into
this when i should have been fair for all twitch employees right so that was my fault um
um but um her actions actions of her lawyers the actions of her corporation the actions of her
community really speak for themselves and um well we will find out what happens here because
while this has been annoying for me to deal with i believe uh it has produced a lot of tangible
long-term benefits in terms of mental health motivation everything in between so um
cool all right until next time